Guide to the Walt Horan Papers 1939-1967
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 2: Outgoing Office Correspondence, 1943-1964
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1962
    - I- January-December; J- January-February (Box 23, Folder 1327)
    - J- March-December (Box 23, Folder 1328)
    - K- January-March 20 (Box 23, Folder 1329)
    - K- March 21-June 20 (Box 23, Folder 1330)
    - K- June 21-December (Box 23, Folder 1331)
    - L- January-February (Box 23, Folder 1332)
    - L- March-May (Box 23, Folder 1333)
    - L- June-August (Box 23, Folder 1334)
    - L- September-December (Box 23, Folder 1335)
    - Mc- January-April (Box 23, Folder 1336)
    - Mc- May-December (Box 23, Folder 1337)
    - M- January (Box 23, Folder 1338)
    - M- February-March 15 (Box 23, Folder 1339)
    - M- March 16-April (Box 23, Folder 1340)
    - M- May-June (Box 23, Folder 1341)
    - M- July-August (Box 23, Folder 1342)
    - M- September-December (Box 23, Folder 1343)
    - N- January-April (Box 23, Folder 1344)
    - N- May-December (Box 23, Folder 1345)
    - O- January-May (Box 23, Folder 1346)
    - O- June-December (Box 23, Folder 1347)
    - P- January-February (Box 23, Folder 134)
    - P- March-April (Box 23, Folder 1349)
    - P- May-July (Box 23, Folder 1350)
    - P- August-September (Box 23, Folder 1351)
    - P- October-December (Box 23, Folder 1352)
    - Q- January-December; R- January-February 15 (Box 24, Folder 1353)
    - R- February 16-April 19 (Box 24, Folder 1354)
    - R- April 23-July (Box 24, Folder 1355)
    - R- August-September (Box 24, Folder 1356)
    - R- October-December (Box 24, Folder 1357)
    - S- January 1-25 (Box 24, Folder 1358)
    - S- January 26-February 15 (Box 24, Folder 1359)
    - S- February 16-March 22 (Box 24, Folder 1360)
    - S- March 23-April 25 (Box 24, Folder 1361)
    - S- April 26-May (Box 24, Folder 1362)
    - S- June (Box 24, Folder 1363)
    - S- July-August 10 (Box 24, Folder 1364)
    - S- August 13-September 25 (Box 24, Folder 1365)
    - S- September 26-December (Box 24, Folder 1366)
    - T- January-March (Box 24, Folder 1367)
    - T- April-July (Box 24, Folder 1368)
    - T- August-December (Box 24, Folder 1369)
    - U- January-December; V- January-December (Box 24, Folder 1370)
    - W- January-February 15 (Box 24, Folder 1371)
    - W- February 16-March (Box 24, Folder 1372)
    - W- April-May (Box 24, Folder 1373)
    - W- June-July (Box 24, Folder 1374)
    - W- August-September (Box 24, Folder 1375)
    - W- October-December (Box 24, Folder 1376)
    - X, Y, Z- January-December (Box 24, Folder 1377)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1963
    - A- January-April (Box 24, Folder 1378)
    - A- May-October 14 (Box 24, Folder 1379)
    - A- October 17-December (Box 24, Folder 1380)
    - B- January-February 15 (Box 24, Folder 1381)
    - B- February 16-March 20 (Box 24, Folder 1382)
    - B- March 21-April (Box 24, Folder 1383)
    - B- May-June 10 (Box 24, Folder 1384)
    - B- June 12-July (Box 24, Folder 1385)
    - B- August-September (Box 24, Folder 1386)
    - B- October-December (Box 24, Folder 1387)
    - C- January-February (Box 24, Folder 1388)
    - C- March-May 20 (Box 24, Folder 1389)
    - C- May 21-August 20 (Box 24, Folder 1390)
    - C- August 22-December (Box 24, Folder 1391)
    - D- January-March (Box 24, Folder 1392)
    - D- April-June (Box 24, Folder 1393)
    - D- July-August (Box 24, Folder 1394)
    - D- September-December (Box 24, Folder 1395)
    - E- January-December (Box 24, Folder 1396)
    - F- January-April (Box 24, Folder 1397)
    - F- May-August (Box 24, Folder 1398)
    - F- September-December (Box 24, Folder 1399)
    - G- January-March (Box 24, Folder 1400)
    - G- April-June (Box 24, Folder 1401)
    - G- July-October (Box 24, Folder 1402)
    - G- November-December (Box 24, Folder 1403)
    - H- January-February 15 (Box 24, Folder 1404)
    - H- February 16-March (Box 24, Folder 1405)
    - H- April-May (Box 24, Folder 1406)
    - H- June-July (Box 24, Folder 1407)
    - H- August-October 15 (Box 24, Folder 1408)
    - H- October 16-December (Box 24, Folder 1409)
    - I- January-December; J- January-March (Box 24, Folder 1410)
    - J- April-September (Box 24, Folder 1411)
    - J- October-December (Box 24, Folder 1412)
    - K- January-April (Box 24, Folder 1413)
    - K- May-September 20 (Box 24, Folder 1414)
    - K- September 23-December (Box 24, Folder 1415)
    - L- January-March 20 (Box 24, Folder 1416)
    - L- March 21-May (Box 24, Folder 1417)
    - L- June-August (Box 24, Folder 1418)
    - L- September-December (Box 24, Folder 1419)
    - Mc- January-May (Box 24, Folder 1420)
    - Mc- June-December (Box 24, Folder 1421)
    - M- January-March 15 (Box 24, Folder 1422)
    - M- March 18-April (Box 24, Folder 1423)
    - M- May-June (Box 24, Folder 1424)
    - M- July-September (Box 24, Folder 1425)
    - M- October-December (Box 24, Folder 1426)
    - N- January-April (Box 25, Folder 1427)
    - N- May-December (Box 25, Folder 1428)
    - O- January-May (Box 25, Folder 1429)
    - O- June-December (Box 25, Folder 1430)
    - P- January-March 15 (Box 25, Folder 1431)
    - P- March 18-May 20 (Box 25, Folder 1432)
    - P- May 21-August (Box 25, Folder 1433)
    - P- September-December (Box 25, Folder 1434)
    - Q- January-December; R- January-March (Box 25, Folder 1435)
    - R- April-June (Box 25, Folder 1436)
    - R- July-September (Box 25, Folder 1437)
    - R- November-December (Box 25, Folder 1438)
    - S- January-February 15 (Box 25, Folder 1439)
    - S- February 16-March (Box 25, Folder 1440)
    - S- April-May 20 (Box 25, Folder 1441)
    - S- May 21-July 10 (Box 25, Folder 1442)
    - S- July 12-August (Box 25, Folder 1443)
    - S- September-October (Box 25, Folder 1444)
    - S- November-December (Box 25, Folder 1445)
    - T- January-April (Box 25, Folder 1446)
    - T- May-August (Box 25, Folder 1447)
    - T- September-December (Box 25, Folder 1448)
    - U- January-December; V- January-December (Box 25, Folder 1449)
    - W- January-March 5 (Box 25, Folder 1450)
    - W- March 6-April (Box 25, Folder 1451)
    - W- May-June (Box 25, Folder 1452)
    - W- July-August (Box 25, Folder 1453)
    - W- September-October (Box 25, Folder 1454)
    - W- November-December (Box 25, Folder 1455)
    - X, Y, Z- January-December (Box 25, Folder 1456)
  - Outgoing correspondence, 1964
    - From Tom Holley, Assistant to Walt Horan, to various correspondents (Box 25, Folder 1457)
    - A (Box 25, Folder 1458-1459)
    - B (Box 25, Folder 1460-1463)
    - C (Box 25, Folder 1464-1466)
    - D (Box 25, Folder 1467-1468)
    - E (Box 25, Folder 1469)
    - F (Box 25, Folder 1470-1471)
    - G (Box 25, Folder 1472-1473)
    - H (Box 25, Folder 1474-1476)
    - I (Box 25, Folder 1477)
    - J (Box 25, Folder 1478)
    - K (Box 25, Folder 1479-1480)
    - L (Box 25, Folder 1481-1482)
    - Mc (Box 25, Folder 1483)
    - M (Box 25, Folder 1484-1486)
    - N- January-April (Box 26, Folder 1487)
    - N- May-December (Box 26, Folder 1488)
    - O- January-December (Box 26, Folder 1489)
    - P- January-February (Box 26, Folder 1490)
    - P- April-May (Box 26, Folder 1491)
    - P- June-August (Box 26, Folder 1493)
    - P- September-December (Box 26, Folder 1494)
    - Q (Box 26, Folder 1495)
    - R- January (Box 26, Folder 1496)
    - R- February (Box 26, Folder 1497)
    - R- March-April (Box 26, Folder 1498)
    - R- May-June (Box 26, Folder 1499)
    - R- July-August (Box 26, Folder 1500)
    - R- September-December (Box 26, Folder 1501)
    - S- January 6-January 21 (Box 26, Folder 1502)
    - S- January 22-February 5 (Box 26, Folder 1503)
    - S- February 6-February 28 (Box 26, Folder 1504)
    - S- March 2-March 13 (Box 26, Folder 1505)
    - S- March 17-March 31 (Box 26, Folder 1506)
    - S- April (Box 26, Folder 1507)
    - S- May (Box 26, Folder 1508)
    - S- June (Box 26, Folder 1509)
    - S- July (Box 26, Folder 1510)
    - S- August (Box 26, Folder 1511)
    - S- September (Box 26, Folder 1512)
    - S- October-December (Box 26, Folder 1513)
    - T- January (Box 26, Folder 1514)
    - T- February (Box 26, Folder 1515)
    - T- March (Box 26, Folder 1516)
    - T- April-May (Box 26, Folder 1517)
    - T- June-August (Box 26, Folder 1518)
    - T- September-December (Box 26, Folder 1519)
    - U (Box 26, Folder 1520)
    - V (Box 26, Folder 1521)
    - W- January 6-January 17 (Box 26, Folder 1522)
    - W- January 20-February 7 (Box 26, Folder 1523)
    - W- February 10-February 28 (Box 26, Folder 1524)
    - W- March 2-March 17 (Box 26, Folder 1525)
    - W- March 18-March 31 (Box 26, Folder 1526)
    - W- April (Box 26, Folder 1527)
    - W- May (Box 26, Folder 1528)
    - W- June (Box 26, Folder 1529)
    - W- July (Box 26, Folder 1530)
    - W- August (Box 26, Folder 1531)
    - W- September-October (Box 26, Folder 1532)
    - W- November-December (Box 26, Folder 1533)
    - Y (Box 26, Folder 1534)
    - Z (Box 26, Folder 1535)
- Series 3: Appropriations
  - Subseries 3.1: Appropriations, Agriculture; 1945-1964
    - 1945-46
      - AAA (Box 26, Folder 1536)
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 26, Folder 1537)
      - Forestry, 1945 (Box 26, Folder 1538)
      - Forestry, January-April, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 1539)
      - Forestry, May-December, 1946 (Box 26, Folder 1540)
      - Fruit and Horticulture (Box 26, Folder 1541)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 1542)
      - Livestock (Box 26, Folder 1543)
      - Research (Box 26, Folder 1544)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 26, Folder 1545)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 26, Folder 1546)
    - 1947
      - AAA (Box 26, Folder 1547)
      - Agriculture Supply Bill and Secretary's Report (Box 26, Folder 1548)
      - Crop Insurance (Box 26, Folder 1549)
      - Fish and Wildlife (Box 26, Folder 1550)
      - Forestry and Products (Box 26, Folder 1551)
      - Fruit (Box 26, Folder 1552)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 1553)
      - Livestock and Products (Box 26, Folder 1554)
      - Obnoxious Plants and Pests (Box 26, Folder 1555)
      - Research (Box 26, Folder 1556)
      - Rural Electrification Agency (Box 26, Folder 1557)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 26, Folder 1558)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 26, Folder 1559)
    - 1948
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 26, Folder 1560)
      - Forestry, January-February (Box 26, Folder 1561)
      - Forestry, March-June (Box 26, Folder 1562)
      - Fruit, Horticulture, Nursery (Box 26, Folder 1563)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 26, Folder 1564)
      - Livestock (Box 26, Folder 1565)
      - Production: Marketing, News Service (Box 26, Folder 1566)
      - Research, January-March (Box 26, Folder 1567)
      - Research, April-December (Box 26, Folder 1568)
      - Rural Electrification Agency (Box 26, Folder 1569)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 26, Folder 1570)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 26, Folder 1571)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 26, Folder 1572)
    - 1949
      - AAA (Box 27, Folder 1573)
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 27, Folder 1574)
      - Agriculture Remount Service (Box 27, Folder 1575)
      - Commodity Credit (Box 27, Folder 1576)
      - Farmers Home Administration (Box 27, Folder 1577)
      - Fishing (Box 27, Folder 1578)
      - Foot and mouth disease (U.S. and Mexico) (Box 27, Folder 1579.1)
      - Foot and mouth disease (U.S. and Mexico) (Box 27, Folder 1579.2)
      - Foot and Mouth Disease (Box 27, Folder 1580)
      - Forestry, January-March (Box 27, Folder 1581)
      - Forestry, April-December (Box 27, Folder 1582)
      - Fruit, Horticulture, Nursery (Box 27, Folder 1583)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 1584)
      - Livestock (Box 27, Folder 1585)
      - Production and Marketing News Service (Box 27, Folder 1586)
      - Research (Box 27, Folder 1587)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 27, Folder 1588)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 27, Folder 1589)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 27, Folder 1590)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 27, Folder 1591)
    - 1950
      - Commodity Credit (Box 27, Folder 1592)
      - Farmers Home Administration (Box 27, Folder 1593)
      - Foot and Mouth Disease (Box 27, Folder 1594)
      - Foreign Agriculture Relations (Box 27, Folder 1595)
      - Forestry, January-February (Box 27, Folder 1596)
      - Forestry, March-December (Box 27, Folder 1597)
      - Fruit, Horticulture, Nursery (Box 27, Folder 1598)
      - General Appropriations Bill (Box 27, Folder 1599)
      - General and Miscellaneous, January-March (Box 27, Folder 1600)
      - General and Miscellaneous, April-December (Box 27, Folder 1601)
      - Livestock (Box 27, Folder 1602)
      - Production and Marketing News Service (Box 27, Folder 1603)
      - Research, January-March (Box 27, Folder 1604)
      - Research, April-December (Box 27, Folder 1605)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 27, Folder 1606)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 27, Folder 1607)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 27, Folder 1608)
      - U and R (Box 27, Folder 1609)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 27, Folder 1610)
    - 1951
      - Agriculture Extension Service (Box 27, Folder 1611)
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 27, Folder 1612)
      - Forestry (Box 27, Folder 1613)
      - Farm Credit Administration (Box 27, Folder 1614)
      - Foot and Mouth Disease (Box 27, Folder 1615)
      - Foreign Agriculture Relations (Box 27, Folder 1616)
      - Fruit, Horticulture, Nursery (Box 27, Folder 1617)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 1618)
      - Livestock (Box 27, Folder 1619)
      - Production and Marketing News Service (Box 27, Folder 1620)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 27, Folder 1621)
      - Research, January-April (Box 27, Folder 1622)
      - Research, July-December (Box 27, Folder 1623)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 27, Folder 1624)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 27, Folder 1625)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 27, Folder 1626)
    - 1952
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 27, Folder 1627)
      - Crop Insurance (Box 27, Folder 1628)
      - Farm Credit Administration (Box 27, Folder 1629)
      - Foot and Mouth Disease (Box 27, Folder 1630)
      - Foreign Agriculture Relations (Box 27, Folder 1631)
      - Forestry (Box 27, Folder 1632)
      - Fruit, Horticulture, Nursery (Box 27, Folder 1633)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 1634)
      - Livestock (Box 27, Folder 1635)
      - Production and Marketing News Service (Box 27, Folder 1636)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 27, Folder 1637)
      - Research (Box 27, Folder 1638)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 27, Folder 1639)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 27, Folder 1640)
      - U and R (Box 27, Folder 1641)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 27, Folder 1642)
    - 1953
      - Agriculture Foreign Relations (Box 28, Folder 1643)
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 28, Folder 1644)
      - Extension (Box 28, Folder 1645)
      - Forestry (Box 28, Folder 1646)
      - Fruit (Box 28, Folder 1647)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1648)
      - Livestock (Box 28, Folder 1649)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 28, Folder 1650)
      - Research (Box 28, Folder 1651)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 28, Folder 1652)
      - U and R (Box 28, Folder 1653)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 28, Folder 1654)
    - 1954
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 28, Folder 1655)
      - Commodity Credit (Box 28, Folder 1656)
      - Extension (Box 28, Folder 1657)
      - Farm Credit Administration (Box 28, Folder 1658)
      - Forestry (Box 28, Folder 1659)
      - Fruit (Box 28, Folder 1660)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1661)
      - Livestock (Box 28, Folder 1662)
      - Poultry (Box 28, Folder 1663)
      - Research (Box 28, Folder 1664)
      - R and A (Box 28, Folder 1665)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 28, Folder 1666)
      - School Lunch (Box 28, Folder 1667)
      - Weeds (Box 28, Folder 1668)
    - 1955
      - Agriculture Appropriation Bill (Box 28, Folder 1669)
      - Extension (Box 28, Folder 1670)
      - Farmer Cooperative Service (Box 28, Folder 1671)
      - Fruit (Box 28, Folder 1672)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1673)
      - Livestock (Box 28, Folder 1674)
      - Marketing and markets (Box 28, Folder 1675)
      - Research (Box 28, Folder 1676)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 28, Folder 1677)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 28, Folder 1678)
    - 1956
      - Commodity Credit (Box 28, Folder 1679)
      - Extension (Box 28, Folder 1680)
      - Farmers Cooperative Service (Box 28, Folder 1681)
      - Forestry (Box 28, Folder 1682)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1683)
      - Research (Box 28, Folder 1684)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 28, Folder 1685)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 28, Folder 1686)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 28, Folder 1687)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 28, Folder 1688)
    - 1957
      - Agriculture Foreign Relations (Box 28, Folder 1689)
      - Supply Bill (Box 28, Folder 1690)
      - Commodity Credit (Box 28, Folder 1691)
      - Commodity Stabilization (Box 28, Folder 1692)
      - Farm Credit Administration (Box 28, Folder 1693)
      - Fruit (Box 28, Folder 1694)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1695)
      - Livestock (Box 28, Folder 1696)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 28, Folder 1697)
      - Research (Box 28, Folder 1698)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 28, Folder 1699)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 28, Folder 1700)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 28, Folder 1701)
    - 1958
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 28, Folder 1702)
      - Commodity Credit (Box 28, Folder 1703)
      - Commodity Stabilization (Box 28, Folder 1704)
      - Extension (Box 28, Folder 1705)
      - Fruit (Box 28, Folder 1706)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1707)
      - Livestock (Box 28, Folder 1708)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 28, Folder 1709)
      - Research (Box 28, Folder 1710)
      - School Lunch and Human nutrition (Box 28, Folder 1711)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 28, Folder 1712)
      - Weeds and Pests (Box 28, Folder 1713)
    - 1959
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 28, Folder 1714)
      - Commodity Credit (Box 28, Folder 1715)
      - Commodity Stabilization (Box 28, Folder 1716)
      - Extension (Box 28, Folder 1717)
      - Farm Credit Administration (Box 28, Folder 1718)
      - Forestry (Box 28, Folder 1719)
      - Fruit (Box 28, Folder 1720)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 1721)
      - Irrigation and Reclamation (Box 28, Folder 1722)
      - Livestock (Box 28, Folder 1723)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 28, Folder 1724)
      - Research (Box 28, Folder 1725)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 28, Folder 1726)
      - School Lunch (Box 28, Folder 1727)
    - 1960-1961
      - "Not classed," 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1728)
      - Agriculture Supply Bill, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1729)
      - Commodity Stabilization, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1730)
      - Extension, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1732)
      - Farmers Home Administration, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1733)
      - Forestry, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1734)
      - Fruit, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1735)
      - General and Miscellaneous, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1736)
      - Livestock, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1737)
      - Research, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1738)
      - Rural Electrification Administration, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1739)
      - School Lunch, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1740)
      - Soil Conservation, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1741)
      - Weeds, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 1742)
    - 1962
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 28, Folder 1743)
      - Commodity Credit (Box 28, Folder 1744)
      - Extension (Box 28, Folder 1745)
      - Farmers Home Administration (Box 28, Folder 1746)
      - Foreign Relations (Box 28, Folder 1747)
      - Forestry (Box 28, Folder 1748)
      - Fruit (Box 29, Folder 1749)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 1750)
      - Livestock (Box 29, Folder 1751)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 29, Folder 1752)
      - Research (Box 29, Folder 1753-1754)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 29, Folder 1755)
      - School Lunch (Box 29, Folder 1756)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 29, Folder 1757)
      - Weeds (Box 29, Folder 1758)
    - 1963
      - Agriculture Supply Bill (Box 29, Folder 1759)
      - Commodity Stabilization (Box 29, Folder 1760)
      - Extension (Box 29, Folder 1761)
      - Farmers Home Administration (Box 29, Folder 1762)
      - Forestry (Box 29, Folder 1763)
      - Fruit (Box 29, Folder 1764)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 1765)
      - Livestock (Box 29, Folder 1766)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 29, Folder 1767)
      - Research (Box 29, Folder 1768)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 29, Folder 1769)
      - School Lunch (Box 29, Folder 1770)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 29, Folder 1771)
      - Weeds (Box 29, Folder 1772)
    - 1964
      - Commodity Credit (Box 29, Folder 1773)
      - Extension (Box 29, Folder 1774)
      - Farmers Home Administration (Box 29, Folder 1775)
      - Food Stamp Plan (Box 29, Folder 1776)
      - Forestry (Box 29, Folder 1777)
      - Fruit (Box 29, Folder 1778)
      - General and Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 1779)
      - Livestock (Box 29, Folder 1780)
      - Production and Marketing (Box 29, Folder 1781)
      - Production and Marketing News Service (Box 29, Folder 1782)
      - Research (Box 29, Folder 1783)
      - Rural Electrification Administration (Box 29, Folder 1784)
      - School Lunch (Box 29, Folder 1785)
      - Soil Conservation (Box 29, Folder 1786)
      - Weeds (Box 29, Folder 1787)
  - Subseries 3.2: Appropriations, Army Civil Functions; 1948-1954
    - Army Civil Functions, 1948-1954
      - 1948 (Box 29, Folder 1788)
      - 1949 (Box 29, Folder 1789)
      - 1950 (Box 29, Folder 1790)
      - 1951 (Box 29, Folder 1791-1792)
      - 1952 (Box 29, Folder 1793)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 1794)
  - Subseries 3.3: Appropriations, Commerce, Justice, Judiciary, State; 1946-1962
    - Legislation: State, Justice, Commerce and Judiciary Supply Bill, 1946 (Box 29, Folder 1795)
    - Legislation: State, Justice, Commerce and Judiciary Supply Bill, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 1796)
    - State, Justice, Commerce and Judiciary, 1947 (Box 29, Folder 1797-1799)
    - State, Justice, Commerce and Judiciary, 1948 (Box 29, Folder 1800-1801)
    - Legislation: State, Justice, Commerce and Judiciary Supply Bill, 1949 (Box 29, Folder 1802)
    - Correspondence: Judiciary Appropriations, 1953 (Box 29, Folder 1803)
    - Legislation: Commerce Appropriations, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 1804)
    - Legislation: Commerce Appropriations, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 1805)
    - Correspondence: Commerce Appropriations
      - 1955 (Box 29, Folder 1806)
      - 1956 (Box 30, Folder 1807)
      - 1957 (Box 30, Folder 1808)
    - Legislation: Commerce Appropriations, 1957 (Box 30, Folder 1809)
    - Correspondence: Commerce Appropriations, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 1810-1812)
    - Legislation: Commerce Appropriations, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 1813)
    - Legislation: Commerce Appropriations, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 1814)
    - Legislation: Commerce Appropriations, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 1815)
    - Legislation: Commerce Appropriations, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 1816)
  - Subseries 3.4: Appropriations, Interior; 1946-1964
    - Legislation, 1946-47 (Box 30, Folder 1817-1819)
    - Correspondence, 1946-47 (Box 30, Folder 1820-1821)
    - Hearing at Portland, OR, 1947 (Box 30, Folder 1822)
    - Correspondence, 1948 (Box 30, Folder 1823-1824)